So how to print the circular link, at least consider the void print circular method that will not return
anything and does not contain any parameters.
It starts by checking if have equal equal to null, then return.
And the struct noted content and create a pointer called stamp is the same as H&B and it do, while
loop that starts by printing that -- the data access every node and print out its its data.
And in order to move the cursor to the next one, we use them equal time, the next that we have used.
And while TAM does not equal to the head, it will be because the circular link, at least when near
the end of that list, it will go back to the first one.
So while TAM does not equal to none or in the in the single linked list, but here a circular link,
at least them does not equal to hat.
Let's see the animation.
Here we have a linked list that contains three notes, the first one contains data 100, the second
200 and third 300, and there is a linkage between the last one and the hat.
So we start by making have the hat and the stamp.
So TAM is created at the hat by using struck note at the second line struck note stamp equal to hat,
then do one by using Do we print that we have printed 100.
We have printed that 200 and now we need to print 300 when it reaches three on the last note.
It will go back to the first one and it will indicate that the stamp equal to hat and this is the end
of their linked list.
This is the circular link address that we have reached the end of it and we have printed all of them
using this glue and using this method.
So it's very simple how to print the circular link list and don't follow.
We are going to see all of these methods in action using that intelligent idea and the same way and
using Jeff.